# Glover Olaoluwa

# Software Developer

+2348036254919 info.copdev@gmail.com

https://github.com/gloverola

#### **Education**

## University of Lagos / BSC. Building Technology.

January 2019 - Present, Lagos, Nigeria

## Baptist High School / SSCE

September 2010 - June 2016, Abuja, Nigeria

# Professional Summary

Versatile Software Developer with 2 years of experience in programming and software engineering. Talented at cultivating a collaborative and supportive team environment. True team player with strengths in adaptability and accuracy.

Skills

- Technical Analysis
- Search Engine Optimization
- Programming
- API design knowledge
- Technical Writing
- Software Development
- Collaboration

## **Experience**

#### Bluelight Agency / Software Developer

October 2019 - PRESENT, Lagos, Nigeria

- Collaborated with project managers to select ambitiously, but realistic coding milestones on pre-release software project development.
- Revised, modularized, and updated old code bases to modern development standards, reducing operating costs, and improving functionality.
- Performed software testing to uncover bugs and troubleshoot issues prior to application launch.
- Gathered and defined customer requirements to develop clear specifications for project plans.
- Developed software for both desktop and mobile operating systems, including Windows, macOS, as well as Android, and iOS.

#### **HNGi7** / Intern

April 2020 - May 2020, Remote

 Planned website development, converting mockups into usable web presence with HTML, JavaScript, AJAX, and

- JSON coding.
- Employed coding practices based on commonly accepted standards to establish site layout and user interface
- Collaborated with other developers, representing the web team to establish project goals, projections, and milestones.